[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "If I could take away the money or the women, which would you rather keep?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Definitely the women, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Rob, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I'm really great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa", "New Hampshire"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Well, you must be really excited, because last time I interviewed you, I mean, you -- politics is seeping through your veins, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, look, this is my -- one of my favorite times of year, Iowa caucuses going into New Hampshire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "I mean, one vote, and it seemed to be, once they had clearly decided it, that's the moment to answer all the people who were apathetic about politics that still want change in their lives, it's that moment, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, it's why I'm against term limits, because it -- we all have the power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What are you looking for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "They need to personally come to my house, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Why does it matter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "It was high treason, and it mattered a great deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "If you were in the White House now, advising President Obama as the Sam Seaborn character, what would you be saying to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, without getting into the politics of it, I think -- I think this recess appointment is exactly the kind of thing that \"The West Wing\" White House chief of staff would have advocated, for the president to be bold.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Obama", "Sam Seaborn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Yes, I mean, is he swinging the bat hard enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, yes, you know, just for me, I always compare it to leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Grecian Formula"], "PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "It's like this is a fit guy, aging before our eyes, because it must be relentless, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, listen, I think every president should get a lifetime supply of Grecian Formula when they're -- when they're sworn in, because it's -- look at Clinton.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "I guess that was slightly tongue-in-cheek, but if you were doing it now, with the senior Republicans, what are the areas that you sense most Americans really care about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNPS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, I mean, obviously, they care about the economy, because so many people are trying to figure out where they stand with the changing economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ":", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Are you -- are you able to -- do you allow yourself to have any kind of view as to his innocence or guilt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "No, because it's that thing of -- if you're playing a -- playing a hero, you can't play a hero.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "You must be thrilled, are you, in the way it's gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", ":", "JJR", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "RBR", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What was the single most repetitively boring question that you had to answer on your book tour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "My favorite part about the book tour, actually, Piers, is my interview -- on -- and I'm not sucking up -- more people -- and I did every show on the planet -- more people saw our interview than anything I did, more people were complimentary of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "So, how do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Not so good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "OWE: So let me get this straight, you're running clips of me with a double chin, gray hair, and then a guy who's 100 times hotter than me after I'm on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "For many reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Was that a dream of yours to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "How did she react when you did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "She said, it's not big enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "How did that feel, that time in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "It was taking a step back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "How did you get told the news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "It was like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "As brutal as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "It wasn't as brutal as that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Did a part of you believe that, that maybe you weren't good enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "You definitely have those nights where you fell a little insecure, but I didn't want to give up, I wasn't going to -- my goal was, I'm not going to go back home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "How did you move from has been at 18 to back on track?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I think I grew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What's the worst song you've ever written?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't even want to say it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phil"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 384, "question": "For the CNN worldwide audience, the worst Bruno Mars song you have ever written, the one that even now makes you come out in a weird sweat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Me and my partner Phil wrote a song called \"Bedroom Bandit.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elvis Presley"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "The next day, we called each other up like, what were we thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "You told a good story, that I read about you, when you were talking about Elvis Presley and a bit of footage you'd seen of him performing I think on a TV show, with a big audience of women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Lowe"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Rob Lowe, you hear that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "In numbers only Rob Lowe could dream about.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Lowe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Me, Bruno Mars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Not me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno Mars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Let's cut through all that crap, shall we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "What's the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Is it actually a bit weird?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "It's the greatest feeling on Earth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "You were a good little Elvis, weren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Man, I see those.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you remember that part of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hawaii"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What was early life for you and the family like in Hawaii?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "You know, Hawaii is a special place.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hawaii"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What values did they instill in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "ARS: Just family is everything for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "If I could take away the money or the women, which would you rather keep?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Definitely the women, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "What is this, a setup?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It's a good answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "It's obviously great to have it, but does it mean that much to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Because we're going to -- I can explain all of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Literally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Literally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What do you think brings happiness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "The simple things, little things in life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Adele"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Who do you most admire in the business and why, currently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Currently, I love -- I love Adele.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What's your feeling about it looking back on it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I just -- I don't live my life with regrets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Did it scare you, this episode?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Did you think, whoa, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "ARS: Yeah, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Lowe"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What do you think is the secret to happiness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "To get my hair better than Rob Lowe's.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "You hear that, Lowe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Got to say, job done.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lowe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Is time the real problem when you get as successful as you've become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Just finding any time for yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "And a personal life, time and a personal life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Just to clarify, you're on the market?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "That's right, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Are you a taken man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "I am on the market.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "You are available?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Is that how you describe yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "We wouldn't put it that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "How long have you guys worked with Bruno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Got to be like four years now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "From a musical point of view, how good is this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "He is one of the best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "What else do you need to be as successful as Bruno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "His voice is incredibly unique as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP"], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Do I have to be here when you guys are talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Ear muff it", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "How important to have guys of this caliber in the locker, looking after you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "The most important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Where would you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Bruno, it has been a real pleasure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]